

I am 2 in 1 passionate Wordpress Expert and Web Designer who in the best possible way combines experience and creativity from the world of design into WordPress sites and makes extraordinary creations out of them. Originally from Sabac, and having living and working in Belgrade for years. I have a strong desire to improve my career to a higher level and contribute my work to a successful business.

# CIRRUCULUM VITAE OF NEMANJA TODOROVIC

### **EDUCATION**

**WORDPRESS EXPERT JUNIOR** July-September 2022 IT Bootcamp

HTML/CSS 2021-2022 Cubes IT School

SECURITY MANAGER 2009-2015 Faculty of Security Studies

**ECONOMIC TEHNICIAN** 2005-2009 Secondary school of Economics

## **SKILLS**

Monitoring and improving website performance by using optimization best practices

**Troubleshooting WordPress issues** (error 500, 404, mixed content, layout issues, plugin or theme conflict)

**Creating well-designed, responsive WordPress websites** by utilizing Page Builders and corresponding plugins

**Setting up WordPress e-commerce platform**, including Shop, custom templates and payment gateway configuration

HTML/CSS

Familiar with PHP and phpMyAdmin

**Familiar with SEO** and proactive sitemap submission

Advanced design knowledge (FIGMA, InVision, Adobe XD, Canva)

Bootstrap, Basic Javascript

### **CERTIFICATES**

- WEB DESIGN BitDegree Acadamy (2022)
- RESPONSIVE WEB **DESIGN** freeCodeCamp (2021)
- HTML/CSS Pirple Certificate (2022)
- FUNDAMENTALS OF DIGITAL MARKETING Google (2019)

#### **LANGUAGE**





### **EXPERIENCE**

WEB DESIGNER, UI/UX, FRONT-END DEVELOPER, WEB CONTENT MANAGER 2018- Curent Freelance

MARKETING OPERATOR 2017-2018 Digital Media Azut Doo

ASSOCIATE IN SALES 2015-2018 Merkur Versicherung AG

SECURITY MANAGER 2014-2014 Banka Postanska Stedionica

#### **HOBIES**



Analogue Photography



Video Games



Camping

# CONTACT



+381692220789



n.todorovic990@gmail.com



**GITHUB** 



LINKEDIN